TRACEY CATHERINE SAADA

6 Edale Bank Glossop Derbyshire, SK13 6HA

Mobile: 07786 374892 Email:traceysaada@outlook.com

Personal Profile

An individual described as a reliable, hard working and self motivated. I have 13 years management experience with a reputation for meeting challenges and organisational goals. My excellent communication skills ensure a successful interaction with people at all levels. Having a highly motivated personality ensures that all challenges are met to a high standard.

Professional Experience

Extensive Senior Management Experience:

- Service Department
- Accounts
- Parts & buying Department
- Sales
- Transport
- Call Desk
- > Engineering Department (organisation of engineers and technical support)

My excellent communication skills are invaluable, due to the level of engagement that is required across each service area. The motivation of staff is high on my agenda, alongside maintaining communication with key stakeholders. The success of my management was highlighted during **2006** when the company expanded. My extensive knowledge on all the roles within the company ensures the design and implementation of various training sessions, as well as inductions to the company.

Throughout my time with this company I have had an integral role within the sales department, which involved sourcing new clients, improving customer relations and securing new contracts.

Accounts:

When my career started I gained the basic book keeping skills and covered the first year of AAT. During my career I have worked in accounts, where I dealt with purchase ledger and credit control. More recently I completed accounts on profit and loss, to determine which customer accounts are profitable or running at a loss.

Account Management:

As Account Manager I looked at the costing and care of the customer base at Amdec and the compilation of accounts records. Another task that is high on my agenda is ensuring that my administration team keep accurate records to show that the forklift trucks are:

- Certificated
- Serviced
- Repaired
- All estimates are sent to the customer advising them on the best course of action

Computer skills:

My computer skills are impeccable, with a vast knowledge of the below software programs, I was the one sent to learn & receive training on our current computer software & then train others in the company to use it as well as completing the set up of nominal, cost codes & cross over of info to sage from key:

- Microsoft Word
- Outlook
- Excel
- PowerPoint
- Adobe
- Photoshop
- Internet Explorer

Employment History

October 2000 to Present

Amdec Industrial Products Ltd Dinting Vale House Dinting Vale Glossop SK13 6NU

I currently work as the Operations Manager for Amdec Industrial products. I have been in this position for the past 12 years, with a total of 17 years employment with the company. I am seeking a new challenge, which will increase the diversity of my knowledge.

Operations Manager: When appointed as Operations Manager, I eagerly took on the challenge of meeting the demands of a new expanding company. The company was excelling in the forklift industry, with an ever increasing clientele.

My role grew over the years as did the company, the areas that I worked in required further development, company knowledge and a determined personality.

Amdec have a fleet of over a 1000 trucks and a very large customer base. My role involves quoting customers for work on their forklifts identifying parts and dealing with any problems from the service side. This also means that I cover the role of certification manager which deals with all aspects of health & safety on forklift trucks (I was responsible for Amdec becoming an accredited company with the forklift truck association and taking us to the level to carry out certifications).

My role has incorporated HR throughout my 13 years with the company; staff morale is high on my priority. I have extensive knowledge of employment legislation/law/legal issues, which in turn helped me deal with disciplinary matters or other personnel matters that arose within the company.

1997-2000 Redbridge Produce, Office Administrator

- Customer Service General enquires, sales
- Key Account manager for National Accounts
- Customer Complaints
- Admin duties including banking, setting of accounts, written correspondence, contracts, invoicing of all
 vehicles, implementing quality measures to ensure vehicles are roadworthy, arranging and maintaining
 agreements and processing insurance.
- Credit Control
- Staff training

Education

Tameside College 1995-1997

Computer Studies Course RSA 1, 2, 3 (Distinction) IBT Level 1&2 (pass) Bookkeeping (credit)

Forklift Truck association certification manager course – Sep 2006

Manchester Chamber Of Commerce credit control certificate - 2003

Additional Information

- ★ Hold a full clean driving licence.
- ★ I regularly attend various gym classes and spending time doing outdoor activities
- ★ I also enjoy socialising with friends

